哈喽大家好我是samantha好久不见了那么今天晚上呢是为由我来给大家带来这个服装成业展示技巧的直播那么在这里呢会教大家怎么样去做挂装叠装以及穿搭
那首先呢我们先来讲挂装怎么样把衣服挂在我们的衣架上
那首先呢我们先来导入我们已经做好的上衣
然后接下来呢我们要对上衣进行一下处理把它的粒子间距呢调整为十
把它的增加厚度冲突调整为二那这样呢是为了让我们有一个较为快速的一个模拟
方便我们将衣服挂到衣架上
那下面呢我们模拟一下让它去运用调整好的参数
接下来呢我们来导入衣架那系统呢是自带了各式的一个衣架大家可以根据需要呢进行选择
那在这里呢我们可以承受我们的服装使用我们的定位球工具把它移动到我们的衣架上
调整好位置之后呢我们就可以开始起模拟了
那么在模拟的衣架上呢我们可以选择我们的服装
那么在模拟的过程中呢可能会出现这样的状况就是我们的衣服衣服和我们的衣架穿透了
那像这种情况的话我们只需要选择移动工具轻轻的去拖拽我们服装的面料让它重新回到我们的衣架外面我要参生穿透就可以了
那并且呢我们也可以轻轻的拉动调整这个服装的挂机的位置
那例如说我们肩膀的地方
可以轻轻的去拽动让它调上一点点
那这样呢我们一个挂装的上衣就做好了那么下面呢就是把它提高品质即可
那接下来呢我们来讲一下怎么样去做这一个裤子夹到衣架上的一个效果那首先呢我们先来导入一个制作好的牛仔裤
那同样的我们要对它的粒子间距以及冲突厚度进行一下调整
那在这里呢因为我们后面是使用固定针把腰头固定到夹子上的所以我们只需要对裤子大身的参数进行调整即可
那么同样的粒子间距改为十冲突厚度改为二
调整好后我们模拟一下应用调整好的参数下面呢可以把虚拟模特删除
我们的折叠3D服装工具来进行我们裤子的平铺那首先呢使用连x轴的旋转
把我们的裤子快速的放在地板中间
然后接下来呢给它设置折叠的物理属性这个物理属性呢可以让裤子变得非常的柔软那么方便我们的裤子平铺在地面上
让我们可以看到呢模拟之后我们裤子呢啊就会非常快的就平铺好在这个地面上了那么再模拟一下让它腰头也平铺好
然后接下来呢对腰桶的平铺效果呢可以进行一下调整让它前后腰呢可以叠在一起
然后用好之后呢我们记得要关闭这个设置折叠的物理属性啊这样的话是可以让正确的
牛仔裤的物理属性呢应用到裤子上那下面呢我们就要把我们的衣架给导入进来了
那么导入带有夹子的衣架
然后呢选择我们裤子的板片要选定位置调整一下裤子的位置把它调整到我们夹子的位置上
那么可以在正面当中对这一个裤子的位置呢进行一下调整
让它尽量接近
挂呃夹在衣架上的一个效果
那么也可以放大夹子处然后对我们的裤子位置呢再进行一下精调
那因为呢我们现在挑战的时候护腰啊先夹护腰所以可以把护腰往里面推一下留出更多的空间
我们也把前腰做上去
那么可以前后看一下有没有穿透的力气
情况
以及看一下整体的一个位置是否ok
那么是没有问题之后呢接下来我们要使用固定针的工制把夹到夹子处的位置呢使用固定针给定出来
那么我们可以先在3D窗口当中进行固定针的添加方便我们在2D窗口里面找到固定针的位置
然后在这里的话呢因为我们的腰头是弧状的所以呢我们可以使用我们的套索的固定针工具方便我们去把这个固定针定住的地方呢给选中
那么在这里呢因为我们这个地方有天标以及我们的里外裤腰三层板片所以我们三处都要定上固定针把它固定住
然后接下来呢是另外一片
夹子的一个固定
那同样的3D窗口先画出这个打开的位置然后在2D窗口当中呢去找到对应的板片位置进行固定针的补尘
来这样呢我们两边的固定针就添加好了
那并且呢我们也要在侧缝啊腰头上方给它添加上固定针方便我们待会把步子呢两侧给拉直
调处理好之后呢我们可以给它模拟一下
然后呢可以看到呢夹子夹住的地方哈它的
动动比较厉害但是因为我们一加的表面间距也就是模特的表面间距呢
需要进行调整那么我们可以把它乘3呢改为0这样的话夹子的中间会有更多的空间让面料在里面进行模拟
那么可以看到这样就不再动动了
那这边的话有穿透我们可以对它进行一下调整那因为我们加了固定针所以会比较容易啊固定针拖动那么在脱脱的时候要额外的注意
然后我们可以把穿透的面料部分呢进行脱脱把它脱离我们夹子的范围
然后像这一种呢没有办法拖动的话呢我们可以使用反击或虚拟模特的方式
反击或虚拟模特一种反击红的衣架模拟然后呢把它再次激活再次进行模拟那这样我们穿透的情况就解决了
然后我们可以对这个夹子出的固定针再次进行调整那么可以在模拟下呢进行固定针位置的调整啊
让更多的空间留给我们的前腰
嗯
在这里的话呢我们这个贴标地方有一点也穿透进去那是固定针的地方鼓起来了
那我们可以把那个地方的固定针呢给它取消把进行模拟
那这样就可以解决它一个穿透的情况
如果还有穿透的话呢那么可以把对应的前腰以及后腰的位置上的固定针
你可以取消一下因为有可能是前面的固定针定住然后把它给呃撑出来了
嗯
再次把固定针拖拽到我们也可以把固定针隐藏好然后隐藏的之后呢再进行调整
那这样呢我们就不用担心啊在拖拽的过程中把固定针给拖动了
好接下来呢我们就让我们的固定针啊再进行一下调整
然后把固定针显示出来
看一下它是否要穿透的情况
那没有呢就可以继续进行我们下一步了
下一步呢就是把我们裤子侧缝处的固定针位置进行调整做出拉直的一个效果
那么另外一边的固定针呢也同样进行调整先在正面里面来调整到真实的位置然后再来到腐蚀图
看一下它的一个前后位置
开启模拟然后我们进行固定针的位置的调整
来上了我们的裤子就整个就会被撑平让它夹到夹得上的效果就会更好看一些
接下来呢我们可以在前中的地方呢啊给他加一个故意针
搓碎一下因为前中相会呃有点太垂下去了
那我们在调整好整个腰的位置之后呢我们可以在我们的前腰也添加上固定针
同样的把它移动到我们的夹子里面让我们在3D窗口当中添加固定针
然后在2D窗口里面呢把这个固定针的范围进行一下补尘
然后在另外一边呢也同样的给它添加上这个固定针
一样的在3D窗口当中先选出对应的范围然后2D窗口里面呢对固定针的位置进行一下补尘
那么调整好之后呢我们就可以开启模拟在模拟下去调整我们固定针的位置那在这里呢要注意的是我们固定针不能一下子穿过夹子啊
好先调到夹子的前方不能直接穿过去不然呢会产生面料和虚拟模特之间的冲突
那么我们先把它打开位置调整好然后接下来呢选中我们的衣架然后对它进行反激活虚拟模特
然后呢再使用定位球开启模拟然后在模拟下呢把我们的固定针
我们的夹子里面
好然后可以再微调一下它的一个上下位置
但是呢也不要压的太靠后啊因为后面的话我们
虚拟模特引呃反激火了嘛那么推的太后的话我要就会穿到这个夹子的空间当中了
那么待会一模拟的话呢就会发生穿透
接下来呢我们把另外一边的固定针也调整好调整好之后呢我们来到正面查看一下两边的位置高低是否对称
那如果有不对称的话可以再进行调整
我们去了好后呢我们可以把虚拟模特激活然后进行模拟
然后在模拟的过程中呢我们也可以对固定针的位置呢再次进行模拟
进行一下调整
让它的夹子的位置呢更好看一些啊不要让它掉的太厉害然后调整好之后我们可以把腰筒侧缝
两边的固定针是销让它模拟自然包括前中的固定针呢也给它取消
这样挂起来的状态才会比较的自然然后接下来我们检查一下啊有没有穿透的问题啊有有穿透呢
进行一下调整那么所选呢就是先用选择一种工具在模拟的情况下给它拖拽一下
它能不能把它给拖拽出来
那么如果像这一种穿透的面积较大不好拖拽的话我们可以把虚拟模特给它隐藏
然后呢先调整一下固定针的位置看一下是不是固定针把这个地方呢给压住了让它没有办法有空间去模拟出来
那么调整一下前腰的固定针
然后再给它吹脱钻试试看那大家也可以把固定针隐藏这样的话呢会不容易拖到固定针啊
那如果实在不行呢我们再选择反激火虚拟模特的方式
因为反激火之后呢就意味着其实各处都有可能会发生新的穿透啊那么在调整的时候稍微注意一下
好最后的话我们再次激火虚拟模特进行模拟
那这样呢我们后面的这个地方穿透的问题就被解决了
然后到前腰啊因为我们刚刚反激火虚拟模特那裤盘呢轻微有一点点穿透那稍微拖拽一下就可以了
那这样的话呢我们这个挂装的裤子就完成了
那最后的话再把它提高品质就可以了
那下面呢要教一下大家怎么样去做这一个叠在一起的衬衫
那首先呢我们先把做好的衬衫绑入进来那么前面一样的啊我们要对它力坚去进行调整
然后在这里的话还会多增加一个新的小小的适用点就是这个九宫格我们的显示网格
那这个呢可以辅助我们待会儿
在折叠衬衫的时候呢有一个呃线辅助一下帮助我们找到一个叫对称的位置
那么在这里呢我就提前处理好的衬衫的粒子间距以及它的从头厚度
那么除了这个以外呢还有我们的钮扣要进行调整那么我们的里外门巾呢啊是
呃不是通过钮扣定在一起的啊我们的钮扣是定在了外门巾上
然后我们的
外门巾呢只是通过缝线的方式给定在一起那这个呢是为了它的稳定性那并且扭扣的冲突呢也是要关掉的
那我们把虚拟模特呢给删除使用我们的折叠三列服装然后让x都旋转把我们的衣服平铺在一面上
然后这时候呢它会很做对吧那我们可以使用设置平铺物理属性模拟一下那么就可以把我们整个服装呢给撑平了
那撑平了之后呢我们可以再
在服饰图的角度下呢对这个服装的位置进行压调整那特别是袖子的地方那么可以把袖子呢给它张开一下方便我们待会进行折叠
那么如果有模拟不成这种一些弯斜的啊没有在正中间的可以调整一下这个呢也说方便我们待会进行测叠的
那这里好说我们给它设置这个平铺的物理啊折叠的物理属性方便我们待会对它进行下调整
那么接下来我们可以对它的一个平铺下来的一个效果进行下调整比如说领子的地方也对它调整一下
然后还有肩膀减少它中间的一个重的量
袖子的什么的如果有皱起的话呢也可以轻轻的脱窜进行调整
那调整好之后呢可以使用我们的水平翻转把它翻过来变成背面朝上方便我们折叠
那这个操作就有点和我们真实折叠衣服一样了
让我们再调整好之后呢就可以使用我们的折叠工具也就是我们默认选中的一个彻底工具
然后我们可以单击开始啊然后按住是不见附中门有个垂直的线
好然后就会生存上的一个环啊那我们可以拖到箭头对它进行折叠
然后接下来我们要对袖子进行折叠了我们有一个折叠选择的工具
那可以选中我们需要折叠的版片就是我们袖子版片然后接下来按下回车键
然后再绘制它的一个折叠线
这个时候呢就只会折叠你所选中的这个版片了
我们把袖子呢给它折过来
那么折叠之后呢我们可以开启模拟然后对它的一个折叠的位置进行一下调整
可以加个固定之方便它跑开啊然后呢可以我们去两边上下拉一拉
然后调的它袖子更加
适宜些
那调之后呢可以把固定针给关闭
然后接下来选中我们的直接工具把另外一边也用同样的方法给它折过来
这样呢我们就把另外一边呢也给做好了然后下面呢我们也是使用我们的折叠选择的工具然后选中呢
另外一边的袖子版片
也就绘制它的一个折叠线
然后使用我们的箭头拖拽然后把我们的袖子呢给贴过来
然后同样的我们可以对袖子的一个设定位置进行调整
那我们可以在模拟下呢去拖动这一个面料那在这边呢我最好上是先给它拎起来
然后让它不要和下面的面料接触起来
然后再给它移动到正确的位置这样调整会比较好调一些
那同样的有需要的话我们也可以加入固定针辅助进行拖钻调整
那么在做好之后呢我们下面就对它进行下一步的折叠了那么选择折叠工具
然后把它袖口的地方呢往里折啊那么大概是在它三分之一的地方啊整体长度的三分之一
要给它绘制出折叠线进行折叠
让我模拟一下
这边的话因为它面料比较孤好所以不要让它模拟太久不然的话会滑开然后我们在剩下的
整体长度的大概二分之一的位置给它绘制上新的折叠线
要对它进行折叠
把它翻过来之后呢给它模拟一下
这样呢我们的折叠衬衫啊初步完成了
那么在处理好之后我们来把它翻过来啊那在这边呢我们可以使用这个啊水平反转给它翻过来
翻过来之后呢再给它去模拟一下
让它形态变得更自然一些然后呢取消它的一个折叠物理属性以它面料本身的物理属性再给它去模拟一下
然后在这里的话我们可以加入固定针对它的折叠效果整体的折叠效果进行一下调整
可以这样给它
拉拉拉一下不要让它滑开包括里面呢也可以给它去加一个固定针让它往里收一下
另外一边呢也是一样的
加一个固定针
然后拖动一下往里收一下让它不要有一种滑开的感觉啊
然后在调整好之后呢我们就可以对它的啊品质进行提高
然后再次模拟
那么模拟完模拟的差不多之后我们可以把固定针给取消掉让它整体呢模拟自然
那么在模拟好之后根据这一个折叠的形态有时候有需要的呢可以进行轻微的一个独载调整
那像领子地方如果不平整的话呢也轻轻的就给它拉一下
还包括门筋的地方如果有歪斜的话呢可以对它进行一下调整
啊
那么因为现在呢就衣服已经叠在一起了吗
所以调的时候呢是静静的拉啊
不会有太大的动作不然的话会容易把那个做好的形态就扯开了
那么在处理好之后呢就可以关闭我们的网格了
那下面呢教大家怎么样去做这个折叠就垒在一起的衬衫
Then here, we copy the shirt first
And then we're going to freeze the bottom layer of the shirt
This can speed up our simulation and slow it down
And then we start the simulation because they have a lot of faces right now and they're all piled up and they're probably going to have this kind of situation
There's a freeze that we can return and then freeze the frozen version and then we start the simulation
So when he's done with the simulation, we're going to freeze the frozen version and then we're going to simulate it and then it's not going to freeze
And when we have the shirt to fall down to the bottom of the shirt, we're going to take the shirt off
And then we're going to do the whole simulation and we're going to make it
Press on our lower layer of the shirt and it's going to have a more natural stack of an effect
So after we've done that, we're going to give him another layer of layers on top of him and then we're going to copy the sheet again
And then in the 3D window, we're going to use the positioning tool to select all of our sheets and then we're going to move them together to get close to us
Small square
And then I'm going to take the front one and I'm going to take the Ecuadorian experience, and I'm going to do the same thing with this piece of thin, plate
Cold, there's going to be the next little board, five episodes, so that's all we're going to do, just to as much as we can to increase his modeling speed
I want to Google it, and then I can take the cold Bear's sleeve and slow it down
And then we're going to do it again
So that it naturally falls off
We
on the middle layer of the board.
So when it's almost done,
we can activate all the boards
and then do the simulation.
Let it be pressed on our middle board.
After pressing it,
we will activate the bottom board
and simulate it.
And now we can do it for it.
The effect of overlapping with multiple keys.
So in the case of multiple keys,
we just need to repeat the middle layer many times.
And it doesn't need to be simulated
because if you have too many keys,
it's not easy to simulate.
Then here we just need to
make the middle layer
of the board
and repeat it.
Then we can do
a relatively natural overlapping effect.
Then we can fold the middle layer again
so that it overlaps a little bit.
Then it will have a more natural
overlapping effect.
After we have done the two pieces,
we can select the two pieces together.
Then use the positioning ball to move and stack them together.
I select the middle layer to make the middle layer
and place it on the upper side.
From here,
we will see that the middle layer
is left,
and the center is upside down.
We set the middle layer to the middle layer,
and position the middle layer on the upper side.
Then try to see where the middle layer is located.
The middle layer is slightly higher.
Finally, we will put the top layer of the shirt
and stack it on top of it.
Then we've made the shirt
stacked together.
Then we can use the colouring fabric
according to our wishes.
Then if we happen to be like this,
the button is worn through, then we can put the button to use the panel line.
And that's the result.
Thank you for watching this video.
because it's just a little bit in there.
Just make it thin and don't let it come out.
This is the making of our stack of shirts.
You can try it later.
Next, we will teach you how to make such a dressing effect.
This is to put half of our top clothes into our pants.
First, we pour in the top clothes and pants we made.
Then, adjust the diameter and width of the pleats.
Adjust the surface diameter to 0.
Next, we use the tool of the group to put our pants,
top and bottom pieces of our top clothes,
as well as the sleeves and collar to be grouped.
Because these panels behind us
will have to do frequent motion reaction fire
as well as the adjustment of the looseness and the adjustment of the layers.
It is convenient for us to choose one of the panels after we have done this.
Then all the panels will be selected.
First, we turn the pants back on and hide it.
Then simulate it.
Next, adjust the tail-shape looseness of our top.
Tighten it up and make it a close-up effect.
It is convenient for us to put the pants in.
Oh, sorry.
Next, hide our pants.
Then, in this place where we want to put it in,
set a rule for it.
Then pay attention here.
We set a rule for it.
Just set a little bit.
No need to set a large piece.
Because if you set a large piece,
the amount of motion will be less.
Then it may cause the back of this
the amount of motion is not enough.
Then the clothes and people will run to the outside of the pants.
So here, the rule is not to set too much.
Set a small area.
This is the center where you want to put it in.
Just set it for it.
Then, continue to reduce the shrinkage of the clothes.
Then it becomes a more close-up effect.
And then adjust its tail-shape shrinkage.
Let it shrink up.
This is probably to put the clothes on the outside of the pants.
So we can shrink it up first.
In the process of shrinking,
we can use this
Choose a tool to adjust the position.
Let it shrink up.
Because of the friction,
it may be pulled down below.
Then you don't have to go up.
Then we adjust it again.
Adjust the length again.
Take off.
Then as long as the bottom of this dress
Run to about the same position.
That's it.
Then we freeze the pants.
Then simulate it.
Because we don't have much space now.
So the clothes may run to the outside.
Then we can give him the pants.
Go to a layer.
Then we can keep our clothes.
The integrated simulation is inside the pants.
Then the next thing is to cut our pants.
Then the whole thing is simulated together.
Make it look more natural.
Then after the simulation.
The pants are also frozen.
Turn this into zero.
Must be zero.
Otherwise,
This dress can't be put on the outside of the pants.
Then we put the shrink of the clothes back.
First of all, let's put his tail shrink.
Let him relax again.
Can have this amount
Put it on the outside of the pants.
So here we put it.
Let's adjust its position.
Don't let it fall into the pants.
And we shrink it.
It's 10% each.
Then simulate it.
10% each simulation.
Don't adjust it too much at once.
Otherwise, it will easily blow up the clothes.
Then we continue to adjust it.
Adjust it to 100.
Then give him a simulation.
Let him.
The bottom of the clothes.
Most of them are outside the pants.
Then we will adjust the
Tilt of his gold.
I'm going to put this down slowly.
And then when you put it.
Pay attention to it.
Try not to have this kind of hole.
If there is a hole,
Keep adjusting.
Because the amount of the back is getting more and more.
If you don't adjust it,
It may cause a more and more serious hole behind it.
Then we change it to 90.
Give him a simulation.
And then pull it a little bit.
Don't let him run to the clothes.
Don't let him run to the outside of the pants.
And then finally adjust it back to the original 100%.
Then simulate it again.
Okay, that's it.
That's it.
We put the whole clothes out.
And then we're going to take our pants off.
And then simulate it.
Make his shape more natural.
After we add this.
We can cancel our fixer.
It's canceled.
He won't run out.
Just put this fixer on it.
And delete it.
And then we're going to show our pants.
And then we're going to simulate the whole thing.
And then we can adjust the model's posture.
So we can do it in the software.
In the collection page.
Download our official website.
Some of the free materials on the collection.
There will be a lot of posture in it.
New models and so on.
You can download and use it.
Then we climb the posture.
And then we're going to change it.
After we've changed it.
We're going to simulate it again.
And then we're going to adjust it.
The whole effect of this posture.
It turns out to be.
Make it look better.
And then we can hide the pants.
And then.
If you want to adjust it.
It's not easy to drag your clothes out.
Give him a fixed pin in the middle.
And then we can hide the pants together.
And then.
From the inside.
Look outside.
Such a perspective.
Do clothes.
One.
well.
A bright adjustment.
For example, this side.
We're going to turn it out.
You can adjust it a little bit more.
It's going to look better.
It's going to include.
You can push this fabric in the middle.
Let him try to put it in the middle.
It's going to have a better effect.
After adjusting one side.
I can.
Show the pants.
Look at the effect.
And then.
Let's adjust the other side.
The same from the inside.
The perspective is adjusted.
It's going to be easier to adjust.
Because our clothes are loose.
He's got this part inside.
So if you adjust it from the outside.
It's hard to adjust.
The same.
You can put it on the bright side.
Put it in the middle.
What about this process?
Don't pay attention to it.
Selected the fixed needle.
Move the fixed needle.
If you're afraid.
If you accidentally touch the fixed needle.
You can hide the fixed needle.
Adjust it again.
So after we're done.
We can.
Put our fixed needle.
Delete.
And then.
Do the overall simulation.
But if you find.
The back of the foot needs to be adjusted.
A slight pull.
And then we're going to.
Use our function to improve quality.
I'm going to turn it into a high-quality state.
And then we're going to simulate it again.
And then we're going to.
This one.
The effect of the eardrum.
It's done.
Isn't it simple?
You can try it on the back.
And then we're going to do it.
The effect of the coat in the waist.
First of all.
We're going to take this.
T-shirt and pants.
To get in.
That's the same.
This one.
I've set up a group in advance.
So the pants.
Give it a reverse fire.
And then give him.
T-shirt.
Use this tail shrink.
Let him.
Stick to.
Wear well.
And then we're going to.
The pants.
Activate.
And set up.
It's convenient.
We're going to simulate.
Avoid this.
The clothes.
Run out.
So let him.
All the pants.
After the simulation.
We're going to.
This one.
The clothes.
Take off.
And then we're going to simulate it again.
And then the whole thing.
Can be natural.
And then we're going to.
Slowly put his thoughts back.
And then.
It's not a.
What it's not a.
About a hundred percent.
We make a more natural.
An effect.
Then how many.
We can put the.
The layer of the cloth.
Redoing.
As zero.
And then.
And our.
The jacket.
Give him.
Can't get in.
And here.
We just need to.
The clothes.
That's it.
I don't want to open it.
It's not.
After.
You.
After that, we can select the left and right sides of our jacket.
Then move it so that it doesn't overlap with our original side.
Then we use the positioning ball at the 3D window to adjust the position of our jacket to the position of the buttocks.
Then freeze the other T-shirts and pants.
Then we use the fixer to fix the sleeves.
It's the same as when we actually wear this jacket, it's the same as when we actually wear this jacket,
we'll take the sleeves first, so it's the same here.
Fix the sleeves first and then simulate.
Then in the process of simulation, you can adjust the position of this sleeve fixer.
Then it can pull our clothes apart.
Let's adjust the position of the sleeves as high as possible.
Now, we'll select all the jacket pieces, move them to the center of our waist.
Then we'll start the simulation again.
Then we choose the fixer in the sleeves, and slowly adjust the position of the sleeves.
The first is the waist.
Then the second is the waist.
Then we move the waist to the waist.
turn it over and pull it to the front of our body.
In this way, our jacket can go around our back.
When you pull it here, be careful not to pull it too fast when you pull it.
Otherwise, it is easy to have a penetrating situation.
In addition, you can hide the camera model up.
So when you adjust it, its vision will be better.
Then we can see if there is any problem with the effect it brings.
The sleeve is a little twisted here, so adjust its position a little bit.
When adjusting, you can tighten the sleeve a little bit.
It doesn't matter, just pull it forward a little bit.
In this way, the effect of the machine will be more intense.
It will be tighter.
Then the sleeve on the other side will also be pulled outward a little bit.
Then its height is a little different, so adjust its height a little bit.
Then you can see that it is symmetrical on the left and right.
On the left side, it is a little bit obvious.
It should not be symmetrical.
Then we adjust it for it.
Then you can use the move tool to adjust it a little bit.
And now we're going to look at the fixer.
Then put the fixer on the sleeve, right on the sleeve.
Then we'll simulate it.
So that's our accomodation.
Then we can use the location tool.
and then cross it.
Drag the fixer to cross the sleeve.
Before we tie the last knot,
let's see if there is any problem with the shape of the clothes.
If there is a problem, we need to adjust it here in time,
because it is not easy to adjust after the knot is finished.
Here we can see that
after the fixer is raised,
its curve is more serious.
In this case, it must be adjusted well.
First of all, it can be used.
It is easier to choose a moving tool to drag and adjust.
When the adjustment is not good,
like this situation,
we need to hide our large-scale pattern
to see what the state is inside.
Here we can see that
it is more serious on the outside,
so we have to adjust the whole thing.
Then we can hide the clothes
and drag it inside.
This will be easier to adjust.
Next, let's see how to adjust the length of the fabric.
First, we need to adjust the length of the fabric.
We can adjust the length of the fabric
by dragging it inside.
If it is too tight here,
we need to adjust it a little bit.
Otherwise,
it will not have enough
volume of fabric
for it to be dragged
and adjusted.
Then we will adjust it
when it is almost OK.
We are then able to bring down the fabric
and adjust the curling thread a little further,
which helps to adjust the length of the fabric.
The next process is starting the Texas
etc.
We need to compare left and right many times to see the difference.
After adjusting it, let's see if the overall position of the clothes is biased.
If it is biased, let's adjust the position again in the vertical position.
I can adjust the position of the neckline to make it tighter.
After adjusting it, we can start to tie the knot.
Before tying the knot, we need to freeze the outer layer of the shirt.
To simulate the knot of the sleeves.
Otherwise, in the process of tying the knot, the outer layer of the shirt will be torn off.
And its position will be twisted.
Next, we use a pinball to adjust the opening of the sleeve.
After adjusting it, we use a pinball to pull the sleeve out.
Next, adjust the position of the pinball.
Put it through the sleeve.
Here, you may need a more skilled pinball application.
When adjusting, you need to observe the pinball from a different angle.
See if the pinball is in the correct position.
We can slowly pull it out.
Then, the other side of the sleeve can be adjusted accordingly.
Push it in, then pull it up.
To make it easier to tighten the knot.
After adjusting it, we can remove the pinball that just pulled out of the sleeve.
This way, we can tighten the knot.
Then, we continue to adjust the position of the sleeve.
Pull it up and down.
Tighten it slowly.
We can't tighten it here.
If we tighten it here, it will be easy to pierce the pinball.
Pull it up, we will see that the sleeve is in the correct position.
This is from the side of the sleeve.
The position of the pinball can be adjusted by pushing it a little.
Push the pinball a little, it will be easier to tighten it.
Then, we can start on the other side.
Push a little.
Don't forget to tighten it.
Then, it should be in the correct position.
We are like this now, one up and one down.
Then tighten it, and then you can drag the knot part up and down.
Then we are going to use this fake red tool.
Then set a few fake reds where it is tied.
Because later we will put the table down and adjust the posture of the model.
If you don't set it, it will be in the process of adjustment.
In the process of changing the posture, this will be cut open.
When we are going to set this fake red needle, we are going to set it on two sleeves.
Don't set it on one sleeve.
We can use the 2D window support to check if the position of the fake red needle is correct.
Then this fake red needle is enough to add two or three.
Don't just add one side now.
You can also make another knot.
Draw one side and add this fake red needle to it.
In this way, our fake red needle is added.
After adjustment, we are going to put our sleeves down slowly.
First of all, we use the fixing needle to fix it.
When the sleeve is in the process of adjustment,
First, move it down.
You can turn it around and move it down.
After you put it down, we will remove the fixing needle.
In this way, when it falls down, it will not touch the other plates in the process of adjustment.
Then break the shape of the other plates.
Then the other side.
Also give it to the fake red needle.
Let's grind it together.
Then it's a little bit long.
It's a little bit down.
Then you can use that.
Use a tool to drag it up a little bit.
Now, if this knot is not tight, it doesn't matter.
After we change the position, we will adjust it.
Then adjust it again.
We can activate all the plates.
Then do it all together.
Then, because we are in the process of drawing,
In order to prevent it from taking off,
So we can give the sleeve a real shape.
Then next, we will introduce our new posture.
If the shape is altered,
We can see that the shape of the sleeve in this process is not very noticeable.
This is also a way to prevent the knot from slipping.
There is also a method.
Then we will grind it again.
Then we need to adjust some posture details.
So we can improve its quality first.
In this way, it is convenient for us to see some detailed posture.
After grinding, we can,
In addition to the sleeve,
The other plates are frozen.
Including the large sleeve plates of our jacket.
Also freeze it.
Don't cover it.
Then we can adjust the shape.
Otherwise,
After it improves its quality,
There is no better change in the shape.
Then the sleeve can be frozen.
Prevent it from slipping.
Then we can gently drag it with our hands.
If the knot is not very serious,
Then through this drag,
We can tighten it.
Then we can,
First of all,
Use the most convenient way to adjust the knot effect.
And if it doesn't work,
Then we can only use our pin.
Drag it again.
That is to say, pull it up and down.
Tighten it.
Then here,
After we add the pin,
Use the positioning tool to slowly move it up.
In the process,
Be careful not to pierce between the plates.
Pull it up.
Then here,
We can delete our pin.
Otherwise,
If we pull it here,
The state of mind will not be able to pass.
Its position of the sleeve will not be able to pass.
After that,
Then we can grind it again.
Then we can cooperate with our moving tool.
To adjust.
Then the sleeve below,
We can also use the positioning tool to pull it down.
Put two together.
One up and one down.
Let it tighten.
After tightening,
We can use the pin.
Put the knot part together with the pin.
Then,
Put the sleeve of our knot.
Put it down with the pin.
Then the sleeve on the other side
Also needs to be fixed with a pin like this.
Then we start the simulation.
At this time,
Even if we don't use the pin,
Slowly sew it down.
Don't worry.
It's going to break this knot.
Then you can choose a moving tool for it.
To prevent it from falling down quickly.
And then,
The simulation is in the correct position.
Then we can see it here.
Because the pin is fixed.
This sleeve.
The sleeve part.
So it feels harder.
Then we can put the pin.
Reduce the pin loss.
Then grind it again.
Let it not be a hard one.
A hold effect.
Then the other side.
We can see the need.
Don't touch it.
It can also be used.
Tilt it.
Then we will adjust its ruler area as well.
So that it can.
It can be simulated as a knot.
It's more natural.
Then after the simulation.
We can put another side back.
The ruler can also be cancelled.
Then simulate again.
Then let's go.
Our waist and shoulder knot.
The effect is complete.
Will be very simple.
So.
You can also try it on the back.
Then we can do it on the left side.
It can also be hidden all the time.
It looks more beautiful.
And then we're going to take these
I'm going to pour all these items into our scene.
Go with it
We can put our
Pour in the finished items.
Let's pour in a
The sound of a hanger
And then what's next?
Use our selection model
And the tools of the costume
Put our this board and clothes together to select
That's because our scene is a background.
Also selected
You can click on this option
And then in the 2D window
Put this
The unselected board is also filled in.
And then you can use the location.
For our overall clothes and clothes
Adjust the position
And then we're going to change it to this one.
On the shelf
Then slowly zoom in on its position
Make a small adjustment
To make this effect on the shelf
And so
Our long-term combination is complete.
And finally
We'll do it
Open our camera window
And we can set the size of the picture.
For example, set it to this
1920x1080
It's a horizontal one.
And then you can set the direction
And then if you need it
You can set the atmosphere light
And then show it
And so we have a whole
The poster picture is done.
So you can also try it out.
So today our live broadcast is over here.
Thank you for your support.